

M. Mirmousavi

Front End Developer

Profile

My name is M. Mirmousavi; I am 30 years old.

I am a full-time web developer. I have more than 10 years of experience in software development.

Most of my activities revolve around the Web, and in recent years I have also been working on hybrid mobile applications.

I am especially interested in Front End and I am focusing my efforts in this area. Along with my main expertise, I have worked on other tasks like Back End, SysAdmin, DevOps to fulfill my own requirements, but my special expertise is Front End.

During my career, I have always been a Linux user and that's why I am well acquainted with DevOps and SysAdmin.

I am always on the hunt fornew technologies properly.

Employment History

Senior Front End Developer at Snapp, ~ 2 Year's

April 2017 - Present

Snapp is largest ride-hailing app in Iran.

Building Web Applications with Vue.js and React for example Progressive App,
Corporate Portal, and Back-Office

Front End Developer at KarBaTo, 6 Month's

October 2016 - March 2017

I have been working as a freelancer.

- Building Web Applications and Mobile Applications with Javascript (Cordova, Ionic)
- Building Android Applications with Android SDK.
- Building Web Applications with Ember.js and Vue.js

CTO at Rasa Web, 1 Year and 10 Month's

January 2015 - October 2016

Rasa Web company is a subsidiary of Kowsar Institute.

- Building Web Applications with PHP, MySQ, PostgreSQL, JavaScript
- · Directing all phases of web projects in the company
- Managing the roadmap for product design and development

Details

+98 912 395 2960 mirmousavi.m@gmail.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

1988-01-22 Iran/Tehran

NATIONALITY

Iranian

Social Profiles

Website

Github

Twitter

Linkedin

■ Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Vue.js

React

CSS Preprocessor

MySQL

PostgreSQL

GIT

Linux

Android SDK

PHP

Full Stack Developer at Kowsar, 5 Year's

January 2010 - December 2014

Kowsar Institute is an international publisher and information analytics business that helps institutions and professionals to improve performance.

- · Building Web Applications with PHP, MySQL, and PostgreSQL
- Configuring the Web server, FTP server, Mail server, DNS server, Implemented Git for version control & etc.
- Writing and implementing scripts to enhance user experience and integrated scripts with the CMS

Education

Bachelor's of Software Engineering dropout, Iranian University, Tehran 2015 – 2016

Associate's degree of IT, Iran Information Technology University, Tehran 2010 – 2012

Aptech, Tehran

2007 - 2010

Certificate in Software Engineering

- ACCP 1 Grade B (C, HTML, DHTML & Javascript, Dreamweaver, SQL Server)
- ACCP 2 Grade A (Java)
- ACCP 3 Grade B (Linux, Apache, MySQL, Perl, PHP)
- ACCP 4 Grade B (RDBMS, SQLJ Programming, Oracle)
- ACCP 5 Grade B (Software Engineering Principles, Software Project Management, MS Project)
- ACCP 6 Grade A (Software Quality Assurances, Software Validation, Verification and Testing, E-Project)

Courses

Software Engineering (ACCP), Aptech

January 2007 - January 2010